I should have sent him away earlier.
Lan Kexing girl,
what happened to you to end up like this?
Who is she?
She’s Hao Ruichi’s sister.
Hao Piaoliang.
Sister,
it seems my brother coming to Earth wasn’t a wasted trip after all.
This trip to Earth Star was not in vain.
Star Girl,
please save Hao Ruichi!
He looks like he can’t make it.
I really can’t stand
this touching tragic drama of yours.
Don’t worry,
he won’t die.
Hao Ruichi.
Hao Ruichi!
Qi Miao.
Long time no see.
Sister,
how are you feeling now?
I’m fine.
But no more crying in the future.
It makes you less adorable.
Idiot.
You scared me to death just now!
I told you,
I’ll always be with you.
Kiss her!
Hurry up, kiss her!
Uh,
I’m going to make some goji berry porridge.
You guys keep talking.
Seriously, she’s so silly,
but so cute.
She’s really clever.
What are you here for?
What,
not happy to see your sister?
Well, now you’ve seen me,
so go back.
I just saved your life,
and that’s how you talk to me?
Not cute at all.
So...
Are you here to take me back?
I know you're not willing to.
But I can take you away anytime now.
After all, you can't beat me right now.
Just kidding with you.
So?
Did I scare you?
Don't worry.
Since you have a reason to stay,
I can grant you some time off.
However,
your time is limited.
You're so beautiful.
Don't misunderstand.
I was just calling your name.
My name is Qi Dongdong.
Nice to meet you.
This planet
is quite interesting.
Actually,
I’m pretty interesting myself.
First time here, right?
Allow me to introduce it a bit.
Here,
take a look.
This is called an air conditioner.
Just press this button,
and cool air will blow out.
This is a television.
It allows you to watch
all kinds of stories about our planet.
If you have time,
I can join you to check it out.
You're quite interesting.
My irresistible charm again.
Beautiful.
Let me show you the other rooms.
You’re not calling me 'sis' even though you're younger.
You're quite bold, huh?
Since Hao Ruichi is fine now,
let’s head back.
Why are you leaving in such a hurry?
I was planning to cook something nice for them.
The Goddess wouldn’t come here for no reason this time.
If we don't leave now,
there's a chance she might take us back to Lanke Star anytime.
But I think she seems pretty nice.
Don't be fooled by her appearance.
She is the scariest woman on our Blue Ke Star.
What do you mean?
You said she wants to take Hao Ruichi away?
No way.
Hao Ruichi just got his life back, and now he's going to be taken away again?
What about Miaomiao?
Now they'll have to figure out something on their own.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here, he won't die.
Pretty Sis.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
I was about to sleep.
But your Earth star's food is too delicious.
Now I'm hungry again.
How about I make you something to eat?
Yes, please!
This is great.
I just love it here so much.
Pretty Sis.
You came this time to take Hao Ruichi back, didn't you?
What? Are you reluctant?
So,
if he goes back,
can he come back again?
No, he can't.
But don't worry.
As long as he doesn't request it himself,
I won't take him away.
Really?
After all, he's my only brother.
I still want to respect his wishes.
Can I have another bowl?
No problem.
Miaomiao.
I told you,
don't challenge my bottom line.
Are you sure you're completely okay now?
Yes, I'm really fine now.
But seriously, what happened?
My sister agreed to let me stay.
She gave me her crystal.
Now,
I can live freely here.
It's all settled.
Really?
That's great!
I told you, I'm the luckiest!
Thank you, sis!
What can I do?
The younger brother outpowers the elder sister, huh?
But pretty sis,
are you sure you’re okay with leaving the crystal here?
No problem.
This useless rock, we have plenty of them on Lan Kexing.
That's great!
I have to tell this to Jane and the others.
She’s really both silly and adorable.
Do you think this is truly worth it?
Yes, it is.
If it makes her happy, it's worth it.
What is it? Are you looking for me?
Sis,
can you do me a favor?
What kind of favor?
How much longer can I stay here?
How long do you think you can survive here?
Do you know,
living is the most important thing of all?
Before I came here,
I used to think the same way.
But then I met her.
She showed me what joy is.
What sadness is.
What happiness is.
Here,
my name is Hao Ruichi.
I am someone with life,
a living person with emotions.
So,
even if it's just one day,
I will choose to stay.
If you choose to stay here,
you won’t have even a month left.